The kettle and the idol
I'm a college student. I'm a junior in college this year and I go to school here,
I'm a college student, and I'm in my third year of college, and I'm going to school here. That's all I'm really saying.
I don't think I can do that.
I really enjoy it.
I don't disclose what I am doing now,
I'm currently in a seminar,
I'm in a seminar right now, and I'm studying in a particular area that I'd like to learn more about,
I didn't have many friends when I was in college for a year or two.
I didn't have many friends when I was a freshman or sophomore in college, because I went home right after school because of my work,
For example, even if I wanted to go out to dinner with my friends, I would say, "I have work today,
For example, even if I wanted to go out to dinner with everyone, I would often say that I had some work to do today and leave the party,
So we didn't have much time to get to know each other,
But since I joined the seminar, I have been involved with them in class,
But since I joined the seminar, I have been involved in classes and have made friends with people I can go out to eat with afterwards,
I really enjoy school,
I was like, "After I work hard, I have school, so let's go to school.
After school, I have work, so I can go back and work hard again,
I am enjoying school now.
In the first and second years, my friends said it was difficult and they couldn't do it,
Did you think it was easy then?
I didn't enjoy it at all.
I really didn't enjoy it,
I thought, "I don't like school, that class, or that teacher,
I had a lot of those kinds of things,
But now I'm having a lot of fun,
Is this the beginning of April this year?
Yes, I did. Really.
Thank you very much.
That's really true.
I think that the study you are doing now is also a part of the various things you want to do in the future,
There are students from upper secondary school, junior high school, high school, and now university,
Which part did you enjoy the most?
University.
I guess I'm having the most fun right now.So you are having the most fun right now.
I am having fun.
I really had the most fun in kindergarten a long time ago,
Kindergarten was pink and fun?
Yes, I did. Kindergarten was pink and fun,
But the difference between kindergarten and university is pretty good,
I am now in college.
You can't compare kindergarten and university.
Kindergarten was fun. Kindergarten.
It was a lot of fun.
Which is more fun? Now.
With spring.
Is it hard for you to study your specialty now?
Not at all. I want to learn many things as soon as possible,
And I'm having a lot of fun applying what I've learned.
What do the best and second best students have in common?
I have come to understand that the common thing between the number one and number two students is that they are used to blogging and working very hard on what they like to do.
Thank you very much.
I think it is fun for the viewers to see the new members again.
This program was provided by Hulk, Chisato, Rei, San-chan, and Kid,
Thank you again for joining us today.
Thank you again.